[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Black Diamond, Black Pearl and Nightfall are cultivars from this fruit.", "correct_answer": "Blackberry", "incorrect_answers": ["Mulberry", "Blueberry", "Gooseberry"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the name of the Korean gangster that both Kirby and Billy worked for in St. Elmos Fire?", "correct_answer": "Kim Sung Ho", "incorrect_answers": ["Him Kung So", "Sim Hung Ko", "Kung Sim Ho"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "According to her biography, this Hollywood actress once took a bath in 350 bottles of Champagne.", "correct_answer": "Marilyn Monroe", "incorrect_answers": ["Ava Gardner", "Katharine Hepburn", "Vivien Leigh"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Ellis Island was the location of the entry facility used by many immigrants to enter the USA. When did the facility operate?", "correct_answer": "1892-1954", "incorrect_answers": ["1890-1923", "1889-1936", "1884-1939"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Complete this famous quotation, attributed to, and denied by, Winston Churchill. \nDont talk to me about naval tradition. Its nothing but ____, sodomy, and the lash.", "correct_answer": "Rum", "incorrect_answers": ["Ropes", "Rashes", "Rotten biscuits"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "1919 saw the first general, city-wide strike in the USA. It involved about 35,000 workers. In which city did this strike occur?", "correct_answer": "Seattle, Washington", "incorrect_answers": ["New York, N.Y.", "Chicago, Illinois", "Memphis, Tennessee"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie Jaws, Matt Hooper, played by Richard Dreyfuss survives a shark attack in his special shark-proof cage. In the novel of the same name, in the same situation, he is killed by the shark.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Where will you find the first public park in the USA?", "correct_answer": "Boston, Massachusetts", "incorrect_answers": ["Philadelphia, Pennsylvania", "Charleston, South Carolina", "Pawtucket, Rhode Island"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Will Rogers World Airport and the Wiley Post Airport were named after people who died in 1935. How did they meet their demise?", "correct_answer": "in a plane crash", "incorrect_answers": ["by murder", "in a car crash", "as a result of a boat accident"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Not counting Istanbul, which of these cities is located on Bosphorus on the side of the Sea of Marmara and is the biggest city on the coast of the Black Sea?", "correct_answer": "Odessa, Ukraine", "incorrect_answers": ["Trabzon, Turkey", "Sukhumi, Georgia", "Varna, Bulgaria"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What computational device was designed by Charles Babbage?", "correct_answer": "Difference Engine", "incorrect_answers": ["Abacus", "Pascaline", "Holleriths Punch Card"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What do we call this sequence of numbers:  1, 1, 2, 3, 5, 8, 13, 21, 34, 55 ...?", "correct_answer": "Fibonacci", "incorrect_answers": ["Lucas", "Gauss", "Euler"]}]